Toggle Navigation

Utility Navigation

Fulltext search 

Main navigation

    Featured Content [Safety](https://www.valero.com/responsibility/safety)
    
    The Foundation of Our Success. We care about health and safety, and protecting our employees and neighbors.

    Featured Content [Branded Valero](https://www.valero.com/refining/fuels/branded-valero)
    
    High-quality, Valero Branded Stations. TOP TIER™ certified fuel\* and top-tier service at our Valero branded stations.

    Featured Content [Renewable Diesel](https://www.valero.com/renewables/renewable-diesel)
    
    Learn about our production and sale of renewable diesel, a low-carbon fuel.

    Featured Content [Apply & Join Us](https://www.valero.com/careers/apply-join-us)
    
    Find your future. Be exceptional. Learn more about applying for a job with Team Valero.

    Featured Content [Guiding Principles](https://www.valero.com/about/guiding-principles)
    
    The interlocking value of our guiding principles is based on Safety, Environment, Community, Employees and Governance.

Privacy Statement
=================

Privacy Statement
-----------------

Valero is Committed to Keeping Your Information Private.  
Effective Date/Last Updated: August 1, 2021

Valero Marketing and Supply Company and its affiliates (collectively “Valero”) have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and should be read in conjunction with the [**Legal Notice & Terms of Use**](https://www.valero.com/legal-notice) and the [**ValeroPay+ Mobile App Terms and Conditions**](https://www.valero.com/valero-pay-plus-terms-and-conditions) (the “App Terms”). Due to the sensitive nature of the information we collect from our customers, which may include, your address, phone numbers and credit card information, we believe it is important to satisfy strict privacy requirements. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this  website: [**www.valero.com**](https://www.valero.com/) (the “Site”) and how we handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Site or from your use of to the ValeroPay+ mobile application, together with related or linked websites, applications, services, interfaces, tools, payment platforms, software and other functionality provided on or through the ValeroPay+ mobile application (collectively, the “App”).

    When you browse the Site and have not registered for any online service from Valero, you browse anonymously. Personal information - such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address - is not collected as you browse. Valero does, however, use "cookies" to collect non-personal information about how our Site is used. Non-personal information, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Chrome, Safari or Microsoft Edge or Explorer), and whether you responded to a Valero banner ad or e-mail is collected and tracked. This non-personal information is used for the purpose of measuring response rates to banner ads and e-mail offers. Registration for Online Products and Services. In order to provide you with a particular product or service online, we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address and credit card account number (if you are a Valero consumer credit cardholder, for example), for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, checking your bill online, making a purchase, or participating in online surveys and enabling us to provide an online product or service to you in an efficient manner. This information (“Personal Information”) could include any one or more of the following:
    
    (A) Your real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
    
    (B) Your signature, physical characteristics or description, telephone number, state identification card number, insurance policy number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information.
    
    (C) Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (sex, race, religion, color, national origin, age, handicaps).
    
    (D) Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
    
    (E) Biometric information.
    
    (F) Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with our Site or the App or any advertisement on either.
    
    (G) Geolocation data.
    
    (H) Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information, including if you call our consumer customer service telephone number.
    
    (I) Professional or employment-related information.
    
    (J) Education information about you that is not publicly available.
    
    (K) Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this list to create a profile of you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes.
    
    If you are known to us as a registered user of a Valero online service, we may supplement or combine information about your use of the Site and the online product or service you utilize with certain other online and offline information we have about you as a Valero customer and information you have provided to us as well as information available from external sources, such as census bureau data, in order to customize your online experience and present you with relevant online and offline offers and updates. We also use a "cookie" to enable our server to recognize you as a registered Valero online service user when you re-enter our Site. If you would like to learn more about cookies, please read about Cookies for more information. Your individually identifiable information is used to contact you when necessary, such as when we make changes this Privacy Statement or our [**Legal Notice & Terms of Use**](https://www.valero.com/legal-notice). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings, or be deleted from our Site and customer information database; see the -Choice/Opt-Out section below.

    When you create a User Account in the App and then use the App, the following apply:
    
    Personal Information: When you register for a User Account (as defined in the App Terms) in the App, we will collect and store Personal Information about you.
    
    Payment Information: If you want to make payments through the App using a “Wallet Service” (as defined in the App Terms), you will be required to provide us with certain Personal Information necessary for you to access your account with the Wallet Service provider, that will identify us to the Wallet Service provider as an authorized third party. If you want to make payments through the App using a payment method other than a Wallet Service, you will have to provide us with your payment details, including the billing address linked to the electronic payment account and the name registered on the electronic payment account, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information required by the provider of the account to process an electronic payment. All of this information is referred to as “Payment Information.”
    
    Transaction Information: We receive and store certain types of payment information whenever you use the App to make a payment (each, a “Transaction”) at a Valero Station (as defined in the App Terms). In particular, we collect information relating to your Transactions, such as the time and location, the number of visits you make to a given Valero Station, the total value of each Transaction, which products or services you purchase, obtain or consider in a Transaction, which payment method you use (including Wallet Services), and other purchasing or consumption histories or tendencies (all of which are “Transaction Information”).
    
    Device Information and Location Information: When you use the App, we and our service providers or other business partners may automatically collect a variety of information about your Device (as defined in the App Terms) and activity within the App (“Device Information”), including information about the geographic positioning of your Device at any given time (“Location Information”). The App can collect Location Information only when the App is open and activated and you have provided permission for location services to the App. You may disable this feature, but if you do so, you will not be able to use the App to make payments.
    
    Other Personal Information and Preferences: Within the App, we may collect information regarding your preferences, including but not limited to, your preferred payment method, fuel grade preference and/or receipt preference. If you participate in a promotion or submit feedback or other information in the App, that will also result in you providing us with additional Personal information.
    
    Why Do We Collect Your Information?
    
    We may collect, store and use Personal Information, including Account Information, Payment Information, Transaction Information, Location Information, Device Information, Cookies and Other Information (collectively, “Your Information”) to provide you with products or services, to try to improve and personalize our services, to respond to your inquiries, requests or other service-related purposes, to carry out any specific purposes for which we have obtained your prior consent, to provide you with personal offers or deals, to bill you for products or services, to tell you about products or services we think might be of interest to you, to deliver other relevant information such as Transaction receipts, support messages, marketing messages, to communicate news and updates with you, to inform you about promotions, incentives or rewards we may offer or that our business partners may offer, and/or to provide you with payment vouches or coupons, and conduct any other legitimate business activity not otherwise prohibited by law. We may use analytics software to track your usage of and behavior on the App so that we can improve the App and/or so that we can tailor our communications to you.  We may also combine Your Information with certain other online and offline information we have about you as a Valero branded motor fuel customer and information you we have obtained through other sources, such as census bureau data, in order to customer your App experience and/or so that we can present you with relevant online and offline offers and products.
    
    What Will We Do with Your Information? 
    
    Legal Matters – We may use Your Information to protect our rights and to investigate an prevent fraud or other illegal activities and for any other purpose disclosed to you in connection with the App.  We may also make other disclosures of Your Information as permitted or required by law to non-affiliated third parties. We may use Your Information to contact you when necessary, such as when we make changes to this Statement and/or the App Terms.
    
    Advertising – Except as otherwise described in this Statement, we will not distribute or sell Your Information to third parties for the purpose of allowing them to market their products or services to you. However, we may share overall demographic information abo the users of the App with advertisers on an aggregate basis, without sharing your Personal Information.
    
    Sharing with Contract Parties – From time to time, we enter into contractual agreements with non-affiliated third parties, including our App developer, and other service providers that perform functions on our behalf, in connection with the operation of the App and otherwise, marketers, web or mobile app hosting facilities, electronic payment transaction processors and decisioning systems. In the course of providing those services, these parties may receive Your Information, but they are required by contract with us to maintain the confidentiality of the information they receive – they must process Your Information in accordance with this Statement and applicable data protection laws.
    
    Payment Transactions – Each time you use the App to make an electronic payment to the relevant operator of a Valero Station (as defined in the App Terms), we use and transmit Your Information as necessary to conduct that Transaction. When you use a Wallet Service through the App to make a payment, we do not receive your personal payment card information registered with the relevant Wallet Service.  
    
    Who Do We Share Your Information With? 
    
    We may share Your Information:
    
    * With our service providers that perform functions on our behalf
    * To protect or enforce our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, or to investigate, prevent or act against fraud or other illegal activities
    * In connection with a business transaction, like a merger with, acquisition of or by another company, or the sale of all or a portion of our assets
    * To conduct any other legitimate business activities not otherwise prohibited by law

    The information that we receive and use depends on what you do when you visit our Site. We may use information that you provide to us on our Site for any one or more of the following purposes:
    
    (1) Auditing related to a current interaction with you and concurrent transactions, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards.
    
    (2) Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity.
    
    (3) Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
    
    (4) Short-term, transient use, provided that we will not disclose any of your personal information to another third party and we will not use it to build a profile about you or otherwise alter your experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.
    
    (5) Performing services on our behalf or that of one of our service providers, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying your customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services.
    
    (6) Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.
    
    (7) Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance any service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us.
    
    (8) Engaging in commercial purposes to advance our commercial or economic interests, such as by inducing you or another person to buy, rent, lease, join, subscribe to, provide, or exchange products, goods, property, information, or services, or enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.
    
    (9) As further provided in the section of this Statement titled “CONSUMER INFORMATION COLLECTION - VALERO PAY+ MOBILE APP.”

    When your web browser or e-mail application requests a web page or e-mail from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet protocol.") For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use your IP address to help diagnose service or technology problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We use your IP address to send you the most appropriate advertising based on geographic area or information derived from your IP address. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers. Your IP address is used to help identify you, to track activity within our Site and to gather broad demographic information which is used to further develop advertisements, products and services.

    A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your session ID. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests or to track specific data that needs to be available on multiple web pages. Cookies are necessary for the system to work properly. Any cookie in use by our web server is temporary and will be removed when the user logs out or is timed-out by the server. Our server contains links to other related web sites. We do not control or have access to the information that is collected or used on those sites, via cookie or otherwise. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use our products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. 
    
    To learn more about third-party ad-serving technology, Cookies and how to “opt-out” you can visit [**www**](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/)[**.****allaboutcookies****.**](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/)[**org**](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) (note that this link will take you to a third-party website). You can learn more about which third parties have currently enabled cookies for your Device and how to opt-out of some of those cookies by accessing the Network Advertising Initiative website at [**www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices**](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices) from your mobile device. On your Device you may also select “Limit Ad Tracking” (on iOS devices) or “Opt out of Interest-Based Ads” (on Android). The App does not respond to browser “Do Not Track” signals.

    When you submit your information for a credit card application, Valero retrieves a credit report. Valero may also generate and store a consumer credit score and personalized recommendations for each registered user. Some registered users may also receive pre-approved offers of credit while at the Site. Registered users may request Valero to retrieve and generate this credit-related information multiple times in a year at no cost to you. The credit report is typically stored for approximately 45 days. The scores, recommendations and any offers viewed or accepted and the dates of that information may be stored indefinitely. While these items are not sold to third parties for any reason, they may be used to qualify registered users for certain products, services or promotions. See the Disclosure of Personal Information section below for additional information.
    
    With respect to your use of the App, please see additional information our use of Your Information in the “CONSUMER INFORMATION COLLECTION - VALERO PAY+ MOBILE APP” above.

    From time to time, we enter into contractual agreements with nonaffiliated, third party providers, such as marketers, Web hosting facilities, transaction processors and decisioning systems. In the course of providing services, these parties may receive your personally identifiable information. These parties, however, are obligated by contract to maintain the confidentiality of the information.
    
    We use the demographic information in your profile to tailor your experience at our Site, showing the users content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We may disclose personal information to conduct other legitimate business activities not otherwise prohibited by law.
    
    With respect to your use of the App, please see additional information our disclosure of Your Information in the “CONSUMER INFORMATION COLLECTION - VALERO PAY+ MOBILE APP” above.

    While at our Site, we may use information you provide to inform you of products and services offered by Valero and third parties, as well as advertisements and promotions for products and services offered at other web sites or retail establishments. If you click on an ad or promotion which appears on our site without accepting an offer for a product or service, we will not provide individually identifiable data to the third party offering the ad or promotion. Overall demographic information may be shared with these advertisers on an aggregate basis, without individually identifiable information
    
    With respect to your use of the App, please see additional information about advertising and promotions in the “CONSUMER INFORMATION COLLECTION - VALERO PAY+ MOBILE APP” above.

    If you accept products or services offered by third parties while remaining on our Site, individually identifiable information required for such acceptance, such as name, address and social security number, provided to us will be transmitted to the third party only upon final acceptance of that product or service. Customers will be informed that they are accepting a product or service of a third party, and may or may not be subsequently linked to the third party's web site. Third party suppliers might include providers of financial services, credit information, or other consumer products, and may have privacy policies related to their web site, the internet and e-commerce which are different than ours. If you do not want your individually identifiable information shared with any third parties, do not accept any offers for services from third party organizations. Prior to any such acceptance you will be informed that some or all of your individually identifiable and nonpublic information may likely be shared with that organization.
    
    With respect to your use of the App, please see additional information about third party offers in the “CONSUMER INFORMATION COLLECTION - VALERO PAY+ MOBILE APP” above.
    
    Valero may make other disclosures as permitted or required by law to nonaffiliated third parties in addition to those described in the notice.

    Our Site encourages registered users to send e-mail messages to us and to provide us with e-mail and name information for friends who may be interested in the services and information provided at our Site. We provide the registered user with an e-mail hyperlink to refer friends to our Site. That information is stored in a prospect database and is listed as a referral from the registered user for up to 90 days. This information is not sold or distributed to any third parties.

    This Site and the App each contain links to other websites. Valero is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites. Please refer to those websites for specific information about their privacy or security practices or policies.

    The protection of consumer information, including Your Information, is one the guiding principles behind Valero. Any modifications to this Statement will go into immediate effect after they have been posted on our website, as indicated by the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Statement.

    This Site has security measures in place to protect against the negligent or inadvertent loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Valero’s networking systems include an industry standard firewall and systems that are both physically and logically protected (via secured locations and passwords). Consumer information will be regularly backed-up and stored in a secure location. Credit Report information will be kept on our servers in encrypted format for a maximum of 45 days. Other consumer data (such as name, address, etc.) will be kept on an industry standard computer database fully protected behind a firewall. If you have specific additional questions about Valero’s systems or the storage of data, please contact us online **[Customer.Relations@valero.com](mailto:Customer.Relations@valero.com).**
    
    With respect to your use of the App, we are committed to ensuring that the Personal Information we collect from you is secure.  We take reasonable measures, including administrative, technical and physical procedures to protect that Personal Information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. If you believe that your Account login details have been exposed, you can change your Account password at any time using the App.

    Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For this reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 18.
    
    Specifically, with respect to the App, it is not intended for use by children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly solicit Personal Information from children under that age, and we do not knowingly market use of the App to children under that age. Please notify us immediately if you believe we may have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 16 so that we can delete that information. We do not sell the Personal Information of California consumers that are less than 16 years of age.

    Our Site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from affiliates or non-affiliated third parties at the point where we request information about the visitor. The benefits of remaining on our mailing list include e-mail notification about enhanced service or product offerings that we believe may be of interest to you. This Site gives registered users the following option for removing their information from our e-mail database to not receive future offers and communications via e-mail, direct mail or telemarketing. You can send e-mail to **[Customer.Relations@valero.com](mailto:Customer.Relations@valero.com).**

    If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this Privacy Statement, our practices with respect to this Site, the App, or your interaction with this Site, you can contact: **[Customer.Relations@valero.com](mailto:Customer.Relations@valero.com).**   
    
    All trademarks depicted are the intellectual property of their respective owners. Please see our [**Legal Notice & Terms of Use**](https://www.valero.com/legal-notice) and the [**ValeroPay+ Mobile App Terms and Conditions**](https://www.valero.com/sites/default/files/valero-documents/ValeroPayPlusApp-Terms-Eff080121-FINAL.PDF) for more information or contact us at **[Customer.Relations@valero.com](mailto:Customer.Relations@valero.com).**

    California residents have the right to:
    
    * Request that a business delete any personal information about the consumer which the business has collected from the consumer.
    * Request that a business that collects personal information about the consumer disclose to the consumer, free of charge, the following:
        * The categories of personal information that it has collected about that consumer.
        * The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected.
        * The business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information.
        * The categories of third parties with whom the business shares personal information.
        * The specific pieces of personal information it has collected about that consumer.
    * Request that a business that sells the consumer's personal information, or that discloses it for a business purpose disclose, free of charge, to the consumer:
        * The categories of personal information that the business collected about the consumer.
        * The categories of personal information that the business sold about the consumer and the categories of third parties to whom the personal was sold, by category or categories of personal information for each third party to whom the personal information was sold.
        * The categories of personal information that the business disclosed about the consumer for a business purpose. 
    * Direct a business that sells personal information about the consumer to third parties not to sell the consumer's personal information.
    
    HOW TO SUBMIT A REQUEST UNDER THE CCPA. You may submit a request under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) through the following methods:
    
    * You may call us toll-free at **866-297-6093**.
    * You may e-mail us at [**customersupport@valero.com**](mailto:customersupport@valero.com).
    
    To respond to a request, we are required to verify your identity.  We may also need to contact you to confirm your request. You may also designate an authorized agent to make such requests on your behalf by providing us with written permission establishing that your agent is authorized to act on your behalf. We will not discriminate against you because you exercise any of the rights as described in this section.

Personal Data From the European Union
-------------------------------------

Where personal data from the European Union, including EEA countries, is collected on this site, it is processed in accordance with the above Privacy Statement to the extent that it applies. For further information about how Valero processes personal data from the European Union, please see the [Valero Privacy Policy](https://texaco.co.uk/privacy). 

Social Navigation

**Valero Headquarters**  
1 Valero Way  
San Antonio, TX 78249  
(210) 345-2000 

Footer Navigation

© 2024 . All rights reserved.
